wilsoncenter.org 2017-01-30

# Privacy Policy | Wilson Center

### Overview

Thank you for visiting The Wilson Center's website and reviewing our privacy policy. This privacy policy applies to the online activities of The Wilson Center.

### Information Collected and Stored Automatically

If you visit our Website, we automatically gather and store the following information about your visit so that we can track the use of our Website in order to make improvements. This information is stored and used in the aggregate only, and is not used to contact you personally:

  * The IP address from which you access our Website
  * The name of the domain from which you access the Internet (for example, gmail.com, if you are connecting from a Google account)
  * The type of browser and operating system used to access our Website
  * The date and time you access our site
  * The pages, files, documents and links that you visit
  * The Internet address of the website from which you linked to this Website  

### Cookies

In addition to information collected automatically, we use cookies, which are small pieces of information sent to your browser by a website that you visit. The cookies do not collect personally identifiable information. Cookies are used to track usage patterns, traffic trends and customer behavior, as well as to record other information from the Website. When you register on the Website, cookies also allow us to save information so that you will not have to re-enter it the next time you visit. Many content adjustments and customer service improvements are made based on the data derived from cookies. Our site uses a third-party vendor, Google Analytics, to place cookies and analyze the information collected by cookies in order to make the website more interesting and useful to you. Information that we collect from cookies will not be used to create profiles of individual users and only will be used in aggregate form.

You may set your browser to refuse cookies from any website that you visit. You also may opt out of Google Analytics using the [_Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on._](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en "Link to tools.google.com")

### If You Send Us Personal Information

The Wilson Center's Website will only collect personal information which you knowingly and voluntarily provide by, for example, sending emails, completing subscription forms, registering for events, making a donation or responding to surveys. If you provide us with personal information, we will normally respond to your inquiry, request or order. We may also contact you to provide information about Wilson Center activities, programs, membership and development opportunities, products and special events that may interest you based on your subscriptions. We will never sell, rent, or give your name or information to anyone outside the Wilson Center unless you affirmatively authorize us to do so.

When we send you such information by email, you will always have an immediate opportunity to decline further communication. Please use the contact specified in the email so that we can remove you from the list that contains your name. If you are uncertain about whom to contact, you may contact our webmaster at [wwics@wilsoncenter.org](mailto:wwics@wilsoncenter.org)[.](mailto:wwics@wilsoncenter.org)

Please note that the Wilson Center may also provide your information to: (1) a Federal, State, or local law enforcement agency if the Wilson Center becomes aware of a violation or potential violation of law or regulation; (2) a court or party in a court or Federal administrative proceeding if the Wilson Center is a party or in order to comply with a subpoena; (3) a member of the public in response to his or her request for Wilson Center records under [Smithsonian Directive 807](http://www.si.edu/Content/Pdf/About/Records-Requests/SD807.pdf); (4) the Department of Justice or in certain legal proceedings when the Wilson Center, an employee of the Wilson Center, or the United States is a party to litigation or has an interest in the litigation and the use of such records is deemed relevant and necessary to the litigation; (5) a Committee of Congress in response to a formal request; and (7) any other person or entity as required by law.

### Security

The Wilson Center is committed to ensuring that its IT systems, applications and information technology infrastructure are secured. The Wilson Center requires credit card processing be secured based on compliance to Payment Card Industry (PCI) standards. When you use your credit card for an online donation to the Wilson Center, that transaction is always encrypted when traveling over the Internet.

Unauthorized access and/or unauthorized attempts to change information on this website are strictly prohibited and punishable under the Computer Fraud and Abuse Act of 1986 and the National Information Infrastructure Protection Act.

### Linking

Within the Wilson Center Website there are links and widgets to non-Wilson Center websites. These sites operate independently of the Wilson Center and have their own privacy policies. When you link to third party websites, you leave our Website and no longer will be subject to our privacy and security policies. The Wilson Center is not responsible for the privacy or security practices nor the content of non-Wilson Center websites, and such links are not intended to be an endorsement of the non-Wilson Center website or its content.
